[
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "62399ec510536452e756f440",
      "correctAnswer": "France",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Germany",
        "Argentina",
        "England"
      ],
      "question": "Which country won the 2018 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Russia?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "62417db60f96c4efe8d773e2",
      "correctAnswer": "Seattle Kraken",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Seattle Indians",
        "Seattle Sharks",
        "Seattle Wizards"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these is a hockey team based in Seattle?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95009a",
      "correctAnswer": "Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Mrs Plum, Miss Jade, Mrs Scarlett",
        "Mrs White, Miss Gold, Mrs Green",
        "Miss Silver, Mrs Pink, Mrs Indigo"
      ],
      "question": "Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo",
      "tags": [
        "games",
        "colours",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "62417ccd8c3137686862d73c",
      "correctAnswer": "Boston Celtics",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Boston Braves",
        "Boston Capitals",
        "Boston Browns"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these is a basketball team based in Boston?",
      "tags": [
        "basketball",
        "nba",
        "boston",
        "usa",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950088",
      "correctAnswer": "The Jack",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Nightmare",
        "The Flush",
        "The Drone"
      ],
      "question": "What Is The Name Of The White Ball In A Game Of Bowls?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950047",
      "correctAnswer": "Adolf Hitler",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Josef Stalin",
        "Joseph Goebbels",
        "Hans von Tschammer und Osten"
      ],
      "question": "Who was supposed to present Jesse Owens his 100 metre Gold Medal at the Berlin Olympics?",
      "tags": [
        "olympics",
        "people",
        "general_knowledge",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "62417d8e0f96c4efe8d773d3",
      "correctAnswer": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Pittsburgh Mariners",
        "Pittsburgh Suns",
        "Pittsburgh Eagles"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these is an American Football team based in Pittsburgh?",
      "tags": [
        "football",
        "usa",
        "american_football",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518e9",
      "correctAnswer": "Trivial Pursuit",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Kerplunk",
        "Settlers of Catan",
        "Yahtzee!"
      ],
      "question": "What board game, introduced in the eighties, features six categories of questions and little pie shaped pieces you have to collect?",
      "tags": [
        "games"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f871",
      "correctAnswer": "Cricket",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Motor Racing",
        "Snooker",
        "Rowing"
      ],
      "question": "With which sport is Brian Lara associated?",
      "tags": [
        "people",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "6242e859a22452794eaef214",
      "correctAnswer": "The Tigers",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Reds",
        "The Potters",
        "The Bees"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nickname of the English football team Hull City?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]